(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Scriptwriter: Kang Min Ji)
(Director: Im Dae Woong)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Oh Jung Won)
Darn it.
A Mafia can't kill another Mafia.
You know what happens...
when you violate the rules, don't you?
If you kill me,
you'll die with me.
Darn it. Hey!
I'll kill you, you scumbag!
Where are you?
Open the door!
Open the door, darn it!
Give up.
It'll be over in 30 minutes anyway.
What the heck are you talking about?
Why isn't it here? Why?
We're on the same side. You can't do this.
It's coming to an end. Why are you doing this?
Please get it together!
Even if you save Yoon Seo and Jun Hee,
they're Citizens and you're a Mafia. You can't survive together.
Darn you, Oh Jung Won!
You know...
the sense of hearing is the last one to go...
when you die, don't you?
Listen up.
Darn it. If I die, I'll take Yoon Seo with me.
Na Hee?
Check if she's dead after 30 minutes and send me a message.
Gosh.
It's cold.
The blanket.
My goodness.
Oh, my gosh.
Gosh.
Darn it.
Please.
What's going on?
Why has it turned off?
What is it?
Who is it?
Why are you doing this? Don't do this.
Gosh.
Who the heck are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Darn it!
Don't come.
Don't come near me, you jerk.
Darn it. Why?
Why are you messing with me even when you're dead?
If I hadn't killed you, you would've killed me!
Get lost!
Darn it! Get lost!
During the night, Im Eun Chan...
and Choi Mi Na were executed by the Mafia.
Im Eun Chan and Choi Mi Na were Citizens.
All participants,
identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
If you were going to do this,
you should've killed me as well.
Why did you keep me alive?
For the game to end in the way you guys want, I should die anyway.
Why did you save me?
Why did you keep me alive?
What on earth are you thinking?
I can't have a long talk right now.
For now, I should deal with Da Bum.
What...
does that mean?
Did you kill them?
Answer me.
Hey.
Tell me!
Calm down.
Let's talk later.
Jung Won.
Hey!
Jun Hee.
How can she do this to us?
(Cleaning Tools)
(Will you vote for Jin Da Bum?)
(Oh Jung Won voted for Jin Da Bum.)
Da Bum will try to kill you guys when he sees you guys. Be careful.
Why do you think...
Jung Won kept us alive?
Forget it. Don't think about it anymore.
Now, we can't trust either of them anyway.
Let's vote for Da Bum...
and think about what we will do.
What do you mean?
If we both vote for Da Bum as well, he won't stay still.
He will try whatever he can.
And even if he dies, Jung Won will still be alive.
Things will work against us at night.
We should sort it out before that.
What...
are you thinking?
If it doesn't work,
we should kill her to stop her.
I'll go to the warehouse. Something might happen.
I'll go with you.
No. You take a rest.
- Why? I want to go too. - Just listen to me.
The other guys are upstairs.
I won't take long. Lock the door.
Okay.
(Oh Jung Won)
Happy birthday to you
- What's this? - A birthday gift.
(Happy birthday, Se Eun. I got a lucky bracelet for you.)
Can you put it on me?
- Thank you. - Do you like it?
Very much.
Jung Won's not there.
(Game Development Contest)
(Oh Jung Won)
Why did you save me?
Why did you keep me alive?
I can't have a long talk right now.
No way.
Da Bum disappeared.
I'll search for him. You go to Yoon Seo and...
No.
I'm not going to let you guys fool me anymore.
He's going to kill all of us.
- It's dangerous. - Enough!
Hey, I heard you're a Mafia as well.
You and Da Bum are no different to Yoon Seo and me.
If you want to save Yoon Seo, come to the rooftop.
Darn it.
Yoon Seo!
You guys are pathetic.
Don't come near me.
Don't do it, you crazy punk.
Stop this and release her.
Did you kill Kyung Jun and Seung Bin?
Are you happy that you became just like them?
Shut your mouth.
You don't have to take it this far.
How do you feel about seeing me again?
You're glad, aren't you?
It's me who you want to kill.
Let go of her.
I seriously want to do that.
But I have no choice.
I can't stab you, darn it.
- So what do you want? - What do I want?
I will do what I couldn't do yesterday.
Get up there.
- Do you want me to fall? - Yes.
If I can't kill you, you should kill yourself.
No.
Shut your mouth.
Enough is enough, you piece of trash.
Hey. Just do it to me.
You stay out of this.
Just shut up and watch!
But...
what happens after I die?
Are you going to release her?
That...
depends on you.
You won't keep her alive even if I die.
Do you not want to jump?
- Do you want me to kill her now? - That's not what I'm talking about!
I'd love to do that,
but I can't because it's against the rules.
What are you talking about?
Mafias can't commit suicide.
We can't kill ourselves.
What do you mean we can't? What about Ju Won?
She was executed because she violated the rules.
She was in a different situation.
Darn it. I told you not to come.
I'm dying because you threatened me.
So it's you who are killing me.
Shut up and jump right now!
Don't you remember the warning in the freezer yesterday?
Do...
you want to die with me?
Don't come. Just jump!
You jerk!
Just die!
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Let go, you piece of trash.
Darn it!
Let's just...
die together.
Yoon Seo.
You crazy jerk!
You scumbag!
Darn it.
Jin Da Bum has died.
Jin Da Bum was a Mafia.
Hang on.
You should stay awake.
It hurts.
Are you not hurt?
I'm fine.
It hurts.
- Don't speak. - Okay. I'm okay.
- Don't talk. - I'm fine.
Don't talk.
I was going to resolve it.
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry.
I think I know who you are now.
I missed you.
Se Eun.
But...
stop it now.
I'm sorry.
I had...
no choice.
I know.
It's okay.
So...
stop it now.
Yoon Seo.
Yoon Seo!
Stay with us.
Stay awake!
Yoon Seo.
Hang in there.
I'll get you out of here.
No.
Jung Won.
(Oh Jung Won)
Hey.
Yoon Seo.
Lee Yoon Seo!
Yoon Seo!
(Lee Yoon Seo)
(Oh Jung Won)
Oh Jung Won has died.
Oh Jung Won was a Mafia.
Yoon Seo!
The Mafia Game has ended. The Citizens are victorious.
Jun Hee.
Get up.
Kim Jun Hee.
Leave him alone.
If you wake him while he's on the server,
he could fall into a coma.
(Ko Kyung Jun)
(Kim So Mi, Park Woo Ram)
(Lee Yoon Seo)
(Kim Jun Hee)
Do you...
remember us?
You're Se Eun's parents.
What is...
all this?
How was the game?
Was death...
scary and painful enough?
What?
(Ahn Na Hee)
Why are they like that?
What did you do?
Don't worry.
They're all just asleep.
They're unconscious.
But the suffering is real.
All of this was a game?
You guys haven't been here for long,
but you played the game dozens of times already.
Time moves at a different speed within the game.
We had set up the game...
so Jung Won would always be the last one standing.
This is the first time you've won.
What did you do to Jung Won...
that she helped you?
Tell me.
I must know, so I can fix it.
I woke you up to ask you that.
Why on earth...
are you doing this? Why?
In the world my daughter created,
you all must pay the price.
For what?
"For what?"
Did you just say, "For what?"
For bullying my innocent Se Eun.
For believing the groundless rumors...
and driving her to her death!
That's your crime.
(Original copy)
(Applying changes)
Hey. Get lost.
What's this?
- What are you doing? - Is he watching porn?
Give it back!
- Give it to me! - Let go.
- What's this? - It's my phone.
Hey, look.
- Look. - Darn it.
Look at that.
- Hey. - I want my phone back!
(Park Se Eun)
(Kang Ye Won)
(Send it quickly!)
(Spread it fast, you punk!)
(Or else, we'll send out yours!)
(Sexy dance debut, shows hot body, come watch)
(Play this video live)
(Sending)
- It's the celebrity. - Hey, sexy.
The celebrity's here.
Hey, look.
Nice.
Let me see.
- Nice curves. - Hey.
Where are you going?
Se Eun.
Park Se Eun.
Is that her?
What's up with her?
I don't know.
(You have a new message.)
(I want to see more!)
(Play the live video!)
Your classmate had died.
So why...
didn't anyone take responsibility?
They feared a backlash.
"It was a joke. It was a misunderstanding."
"I don't know anything." They all made excuses.
No one admitted to what they'd done.
No one.
So we created this game.
The pain that our Se Eun felt!
You all had to feel it too.
We wanted to show you what you had done.
(A new game will begin.)
(Im Eun Chan)
(Heo Yul)
Yes.
I know you and Se Eun were close.
You should've saved her!
Why did you let her die?
You're no different from them.
Their memories are wiped each time.
They'll never get used to the suffering.
(Jin Da Bum)
It'll feel fresh every time.
For eternity,
you can live in the game.
Please.
I also...
miss Se Eun...
so much.
I want to tell her that...
she suffered so much on her own.
That I'm sorry I didn't know.
If someone must take responsibility,
let me.
So will you send the others home?
Please?
You're not...
completely awake yet.
You could fall ill if you fight it.
I don't care...
about being sick at all.
So pick me.
Please let the others go.
Let them...
Let them go. They...
(Oh Jung Won)
Her getting her memory back.
Jung Won helped her with that.
Jung Won changed the setting,
so she'd get her memory back from the birthday present.
What are you trying to say?
Suicide wasn't an option.
Jung Won actually acted as if she were Se Eun.
She chose to save the kids.
Get a grip!
That's not our daughter.
It's just an error caused by a setting.
Hands off.
It wasn't just an error. It was Jung Won's will.
What if, like Jung Won,
Se Eun doesn't want this game either?
What if getting revenge is just what we want?
No.
We have a long way to go.
We're not done yet.
They risked their lives to save a friend.
Maybe not all of them,
but some of them felt bad for what happened to Se Eun.
We've seen enough to give them a chance.
Let's let them all go and see what happens.
No.
I can't do that.
Move.
Move out of the way!
What about our Se Eun?
She's dead and gone.
(Lee Yoon Seo)
Darn it! I lost again!
- Gosh. - You startled me.
- Shut up. - What's wrong?
- I'm tired. - Hello, Ms. Kim.
- Hey. - What?
- Join in. - Where?
- The bus broke down? - Take a look.
Hello?
(Oh Jung Won)
No.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)